<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<content id="ws_2457316956" name="Ragnarok (VRO)" author="BSOD" version="102" date="2022-04-17" save="0" lastupdate="1650227345" description="[h1]Ragnarok, aka standalone Super Asgard. VRO version.[/h1]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]32x L turrets, 92x M Turrets, 118M shields, 4XL shields[/b]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;This mod does not modify VRO Asgard and acts as a new ship.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Use only with VRO. For vannila version of X4 use my other mod:&#13;&#10;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2446636269&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Huge thanks to [b]@gso25mm[/b], who let me use his turret/shield connections from mod Super Asgard.&#13;&#10;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2430723151&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b][Differences when compared to VRO Asgard][/b]&#13;&#10;- Much more turrets and shields, in total: 32x L turrets, 92x M Turrets, 118M shields, 4XL shields.&#13;&#10;- 3.5x more cost in resources and credits.&#13;&#10;- 2x more build time.&#13;&#10;- Can equip Stormbreaker main battery which can fire ~30% longer until overheat, but is much more expensive (~2x more).&#13;&#10;- S dock capacity increased to 23 from 10.&#13;&#10;- Little increase in crew capacity.&#13;&#10;- Little increase in missile capacity and can equip L missile turrets in center (bot and top) slots.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Hull HP stats are unchanged, especially with VRO where shields have less impact then in vanilla, dont expect it to solo wipe station with fleet. Will go down fast if you dont cheeze it and are in range. I think ship is somewhat balanced when you take into consideration huge cost of hull. Fully equiped Ragnarok will blow hole not just into enemy lines, but also your resources storage and wallet. Costs can change in future.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Can be build only with blueprint, same conditions as for vanilla Asgard. &#13;&#10;Blueprint can be found in: Saturn-&gt; TER Orbital Supply Base -&gt; Faction Representative (Make sure you have required licence and TER faction standing, same as for Asgard)&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Or use following mod:&#13;&#10;https://steamcommunity.com/sharedfiles/filedetails/?id=2447654098&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;But i personally do not recommend it, I really like what Egosoft did with Asgard, that you must jump extra hoops to obtain it, then just simply buy it in shipyard at the counter like you are in Wallmart. Well, feels more like reward.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Ai can build this ship, but I hope resources cost and low chance to spawn will offset this. So ship is not player exclusive.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;Save flag is set to 0, but i doubt that save will work if mod is disabled after blueprint or ship is bought or under construction.&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;[b]Compatible with More Ship Rooms.[/b]&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;&#13;&#10;">
  <dependency id="ego_dlc_terran" optional="false" name="Cradle of Humanity"></dependency>
  <dependency id="ws_1696862840" optional="false" name="Variety and Rebalance Overhaul"></dependency>
  <dependency id="ws_2399395088" optional="true" name="More Ship Rooms"></dependency>
</content>
